BGM
Here we go... Upokami has begun. This time we are joined by Kitsura Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory and Yaherno of Tsubaki Factory.
This program takes a close look behind the scenes at the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We will bring you our recording, rehearsal and other production processes.
Now then, let's first go behind the scenes with the two MCs.
I, Shinnuma, will be performing at the Nippon Budokan on June 10 for the graduation ceremony.
Recently, I have been getting more and more jobs that I have to do for the last time.
I feel that the days are flying by so fast until the day of the show.
Or shooting merchandise to be sold at the official Hello Project store at the end of the day.
We look forward to working with you on this upkami.
Upokami is one of them, but today seems to be the last day of recording.
As I have more and more jobs that are coming to an end, I am finally starting to get a sense of what it's like.
Um, but I actually don't realize that Shinnuma Kisora is the last.
So this up-cami is the last? Shinnuma Kisora said it was the last.
Yes.
So I feel like I'm really feeling it a little bit now. I'm really feeling it a little bit now.
I thought it would be the last time, but I haven't really felt it yet, but I'm sure I'll feel it a lot from now on, so I'm a little nervous.
Yes, I'm Yofu...Tsubaki Baktory is going to perform in Shanghai? Tsubaki Baktry is going to perform in Shanghai?
I heard that you can learn Chinese and other languages for the overseas tour with an app on your smart phone.
And I've been learning that lately.
I've also been learning how to say the number 123 from Fukuda Marin-chan and others.
Speaking of Shinnuma Kisora, isn't he a cat?
I asked him what I called the cat.
I studied it, or rather, I listened to it.
Actually, I heard it's called the Demon King.
So I think I will use it more and more from now on.
I think I can communicate with everyone if I can speak even a little.
I would like to practice and study with everyone in the group as a whole.
I am very much looking forward to the show and hope that you will come to both the Shanghai show and the Budokan show.
So let's start with this time's up-cam.
Manabana Inaba Pink Temperture Music Video Filming Making of
It will be released on April 17.
Watch the music video shoot of Pink Temperture from Manaka Inaba's latest single.
Good morning and thank you for your time. Best regards.
If you had, who would you be?
Just the soul.
Raise it. The sound of dawn.
My song overflows.
Looks much closer.
I want to go with you tomorrow.
It's time to step out
Stretch and step out
Familiar sounds of the city
Raise it. The sound of dawn.
I just want to go with you now.
Today, I'm shooting a music video for my debut solo single Pink Temperture.
It's called Pink Temperture.
The song is called "Pink Body Temperature," and it has a slightly mature feel to it.
It's been a long time since I've shot a music video.
It's the first of the singles we're shooting for this year.
Anyway, it was like a pounding heartbeat.
What? How do you shoot a music video? I was like...
It started with fidgeting.
But at first I was allowed to wear these cool outfits.
We started by shooting a lip scene.
It's pretty much like a pink temper tureen, so I'm going to do it in a very precise manner.
I'm a little embarrassed about something.
He asked me for a sexy look.
When they ask me to lick their bottom or something.
I'm a bit nervous about how I'm going to do it.
We are having a lot of fun with it!
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you okay? What's with the face?
Was it sexy? Is this okay?
запис gre
car
Thank you for watching!
We were just talking.
Overflowing from the depths of the beyond
Voices saying we can't go on like this.
Raise it. The sound of dawn.
My name comes off.
Watch me. Closer.
I feel like I can run.
One line can't stay rolled out together.
From the looks of it, it's going to kill you.
Raise it. The sound of dawn.
I just want to go with you now.
It's fun.
This time the pretending was so cool.
Because it's so cool.
I'm trying to dance in a cool way.
The moment of Come on.
Yes, in slow motion.
I got some nice compliments on it.
I'm already looking forward to the completion of this project!
Thank you for watching!
Raise the dawn sound, and my eyes are the first.
I see it, I see it, I see it one more time, and I want to protect it.
Always Sember Night. Come now, Sember Night.
Familiar city windows
Raise it. With the sound of dawn.
I just want to go with you now.
The dancing this time is really intense, so I originally thought it would be difficult to shoot the dance scenes,
We had two dancers with us, and they choreographed it in a really cool way,
Anyway, I tried to make the most of it, and also the costumes, with the messy waving and the coats, which I've already taken off because it's too hot now,
I am sure there are many ways to see the sparkling inside, so I will continue to work hard on the dance scene.
See you then.
See you soon.
ficar
My hands can play.
Look.
Closer.
And we want to live together.
It's a special show
If you are seen, your
temperature at dawn at dawn
I am now
I just want to go with you.
It's usually cold.
A little soft face in the midst of all that.
Yes, it is.
It was quite cold during the shoot.
I think we were able to make facial expressions that didn't make them feel that way.
I love this kind of scenery.
I'd like to give you all a chance to see the world of this Pink Temperture in particular.
I think it's a very expressive view.
I hope you will listen to the song and get into the world of the song.
able to keep one's mouth shut
равствуйте
I thought the song "Pink Temperture" would be a pretty tune since it has the word "pink" in the title, but I was surprised to find that it was not.
I've seen the music video and it's very cute.
The music video and the music tone of the song give a sense of Manaka's maturity and sexiness, and the music video is a perfect example of this.
I saw and felt that this song has a different quality from the other song, Overwhelming Love.
Yes, sir.
You know what?
I was thinking that Banaka Inaba has white skin, which makes her look very translucent, and she would really stand out in the dark at night, wouldn't she? She was wearing a mature lipstick, so I thought it looked really cute on her.
It was the making of Manaka Pink Temperture music video shoot.
Thanks for taking a look after all these years.
And here's the next one.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 making-of video
The event was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024
In this issue, we will focus on solo and shuffle units.
Please take a look.
BANG! BANG! BANG!
3,4,5,6,7,8
par wave
crumbly (e.g. tofu, cheese, non-sticky rice)
revolving
par
twice
Twice and then cruise.
par
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
revolving
Oh, ya!
Yah!
both of them
touch
Ah, your touch.
Not at all, a real touch.
0.03 mm (one-thousandth of a sun)
with a grinding noise
importunately
heave, ho!
indicates command
Ooh.
Four people...
Since there was no I
So, four people can do it.
I was so happy to be able to do this with a group of people.
I've had a little bit of involvement in the past.
It wasn't often that I performed well.
I was so happy.
I didn't get involved in the winter halo either.
Morisawa, Nashizawa, and Endo.
Yes, it is.
It was my own group, that's for sure.
I was thinking that I would like to talk to you about many things.
I thought so.
Yes, sir.
I am
that (someone or something distant from both speaker and listener, or situation unfamiliar to both speaker and listener)
winning one's first election
Last year was a miss.
I was elected for the first time this year.
It's just that they are amazingly nice people.
It's too good for the first time.
Thank you.
please
I thought it was impossible that I had been elected.
I have really bad luck in raffles.
something really
I don't know what to call it.
And raffles at festivals like that.
I hear it's all off.
It's all that.
It's quite fateful that I personally won the prize.
So I say I'm already tied to my destiny.
Since it is no exaggeration to say that
With the members of destiny
Yes, I would like to perform my best.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
Now the four of us have been practicing together, but there is still some suspiciousness.
So I don't get anxious before the show, and I want to keep up the good work.
No! Because!
I'm nervous.
That's what makes me nervous.
I'm looking forward to doing a song I really like.
At the same time, I want to make the songs I've always loved look absolutely cool.
I'll do my best to research until half way through.
Thank you for watching!
What is a life suited to a fine one? TV for faraway places
Simply falling in love is boring.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was amazing. I was so nervous.
I was more imposing than in practice, and I was glad I could do it in this sense.
It was fun. The three of us. I'm glad.
We were all nervous because we were very happy to be in an environment where we could be free in a good way,
Including me. I think I was the most nervous too, but everyone was cool.
Each...
I was a rose woman.
This group is all K.O.'s and cool, and they chose rock erotica for their K.O. coolness....
I was very happy to be able to stand up in the show as well.
Um, I got really nervous with confidence after saying all that,
There was a part of me that was not convinced that I was good at something or other,
I thought I was going to do it, because half of what I thought I was going to do was done,
I hope to do better with this. I will pray to win again next year.
Yes, I have been listening to the song "Rock Eltic" since I was a trainee,
So it was one of my favorite songs,
I saw people who were quite close to my age doing that favorite song with me,
I thought I had to work hard to have it,
Also, Ako Yumigita and Akari Endo are better than me.
He was younger than me, but he was so cool and had such a great expression on his face.
Moreover, Ichika Arisawa and Eishion Tamura had worked together with me as trainees,
So I thought to myself, "I have to grow up too.
It's very rock-eltic for me, too," he unveiled.
The first song I sang as a member of the Halo Pro trainees,
It's rock-eltic.
It was the first song I performed when I was about the same age as these four,
It is difficult to sing this song when you are a teenager or 14 years old, especially in terms of the lyrical content,
The four of you practiced a lot for the show, didn't you?
It was really cool,
I was watching them thinking that they could do such mature expressions,
I am sure that those who came to the event must have felt the same way,
I am very much looking forward to the growth of these four in the future.
This was the making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 video.
Keep smiling and good things will happen.
Tsubaki Factory's Shinnuma Kisra and
Upkami, brought to you by Yofulna of Tsubaki Factory.
And here's the next one.
Morning Musume。23
Wake Up Call Vocal Recording
From the latest single of Morning Musume。 23
Wake Up Call Wake Up When You Wake Up Watch Rio Kitagawa's Vocal Recording!
Then I'll go ahead and take it in blocks.
Well, let's try one.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
I'm trying to be a little bit bad or blunt here.
Overall, though, it's going to be fun, interesting, and intense.
Please sing with a little more character.
Thank you for your hard work.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
OK, let's continue.
The characters are the same people as in the first half, just singing the second half. Yes.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
Cute, cool, mocking, and suspicious.
A multifaceted creature, we must affirm every face.
Okay, let's go with that. Okay.
Let's get a little rhythm out of the multifacetedness.
A multifaceted creature. Yes, let's go with that. Yes, let's go with this.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
Cute, cool, and mocking.
Cute, cool, mocking, and suspicious.
A multifaceted creature, we must affirm every face.
OK, perfect. Let's try the B melody. Okay.
It would be boring to leave it up to others. I will never waver in my decision.
Me, I don't want to trick me. Wake-up goals.
The first three in a row,
It's a little too far forward, a little too far back.
It's probably more comfortable to ride a little bit behind. Yes, I do.
And the last line crescendos into a chorus.
I would like to make a strong statement with momentum.
Please be a little bold. Yes, I am.
A multifaceted creature, we must affirm every face.
It would be boring to leave it up to others. I will never waver in my decision.
Me, I don't want to fool me.
OK, I'll go get them now. Okay.
Then one, three, two.
Me, I don't want to fool me.
Wake up goal, wake up time.
It's time to enjoy life.
The sun is in this heart
Just do it, just do it, just do it, just do it
Wake up goal, wake up time.
It's time to enjoy life.
The sun is in this heart
I will illuminate you dance baby dance baby dance baby dance baby
I'm just looking for a little more bounce overall.
That's pretty square right now.
Yes, sir.
I don't feel like I'm bouncing.
bounce a bit more
Yes, sir.
back of the head
To Wake up call.
Accent with thrusting back
Wake up call. It's time to wake up.
Time to enjoy life.
Let's get a rhythm going in that area.
Yes, sir.
The sun is in this heart
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it
You're thick there, too.
Yes, sir.
stress accent
Who I am at the
I will illuminate you dance baby dance baby dance baby dance baby
Yes, sir.
or so
Please be a little more bold.
Yes, sir.
I am.
I don't want you to cheat me.
Wake up call. It's time to wake up.
Time to enjoy life.
The sun is in this heart
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it
me
Yeah, ok, it's expensive.
Let's take the site and head first. Wow, wow, wow.
Well, please extend it to the full 8, yes, yes.
wow! (sound made by monsters)
Because it seems like a little bit of leeway.
It's fake.
It's a cry from the soul.
cry of the soul
More on the edge.
somewhat strong
Yes, sir.
wow! (sound made by monsters)
Yeah, like, you're going to pull it out at the end while shaking the long part, too.
yes sir!
You can go as far as you want.
Yes, sir.
~~
Yeah, I'll get him to write it down.
Then the front of Mr. Rapp's
Yes ma'am
~~
Oh, Yeah.
For Shaq. Let's go a little faster.
Yeah, right away, Shaq.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I think it's about the same.
Yes, sir.
Oh, Yeah.
It would be cool if we could turn it around a bit here too.
A little fake and flowing.
I hope we can do it like that.
OK, I got it! We're done! Thank you very much!
I love Rio Kitagawa's singing voice very much, and when I saw the VTR, I thought, "What? I was so fascinated by her voice that I felt like I was listening to the whole thing in a flash. I was so absorbed in listening to her voice that I felt like, "How long did it take?
I thought her voice was really wonderful, so clear and yet powerful.
I felt that Kitagawa-san's singing voice was so perfect. The pitch and rhythm of her voice were all so perfect that it was a pleasure to listen to her voice.
These are the vocal recordings of Morning Musume。 23, Wake Up Call When You Wake Up, and Rio Kitagawa.
Let's have fun today.
It was time to say goodbye to Upkami, who had been sent by Rinumaki Sora and Yo Furuno.
Well, we've seen a lot of footage this time around, and I saw the footage of the Hina Festival today, didn't I?
And this time it was the first video of the first performance on the first day of the Hina Fest, but from now on, there will be more and more people at the Tsubaki Factory, including me, who will be one of the five.
I'm a little nervous, but I'm also a first-time viewer, so I'll just upload the video and see what happens.
So I'm looking forward to that day.
I've been to a lot of Hello Project concerts and Hina Festivals.
the kalpa (eon, aeon)
I sometimes cover Morning's songs, so it's very helpful to have the recording video for reference.
Although the music was different, I was very inspired by the way the accent was put on the lyrics, which I thought we could incorporate into our own music as well.
I wish I could do my best too.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
This time, Upokami's partners were Kisora Shinnuma of Tsubaki Factory and Runo Yahuruno of Tsubaki Factory.
good-bye
The next Upkami will be
Omesaki Mai, Tears in Your Hands
Making of music video shooting
and
Tsubuki Factory's latest album
Recording of Third Moment will be available!
Enjoy!
preview of next installment (TV shows, podcasts, etc.)